<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 11:23:50 +1200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo on Github</title>
      <link>/posts/2017-09-11-hugo-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 11:23:50 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2017-09-11-hugo-on-github/</guid>
      <description>Yea, yea, updates. I have a motivation problem. I have real trouble seeing something through in a timely manner. I only started working on the second prototype of my midi controller last weekend. Version one was complete 10 months ago. I had the idea for it 14 months before that. Hell, the subject of this post was finalized and implemented a month ago. I&amp;rsquo;m starting this on the 11th but it&amp;rsquo;s probably gonna end up being a couple of weeks before it actually gets published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSH Auth with Hashicorp&#39;s Vault</title>
      <link>/posts/2017-02-05-ssh-auth-with-vault/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 11:55:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2017-02-05-ssh-auth-with-vault/</guid>
      <description>Okay, I&amp;rsquo;ll admit; I am shit at updating this site&amp;hellip; blog&amp;hellip; thing&amp;hellip; Whatever, today we&amp;rsquo;re going to build something cool; centralized SSH authentication using Hashicorp&amp;rsquo;s Vault. We&amp;rsquo;re going to stand up a Vault server and use it to generate One-Time-Passwords for SSHing (totaly a word) onto other servers.
Why? That&amp;rsquo;s actually a good question. Honestly, PAM just seems like a shitfest to set up and maintain.
All right, I might be biased towards Hashicorp products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Hubot</title>
      <link>/posts/2016-10-02-setting-up-hubot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2016 11:55:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2016-10-02-setting-up-hubot/</guid>
      <description>So this is something I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to do for a while now and I&amp;rsquo;ve finally gotten around to it. I have Github&amp;rsquo;s Hubot running on a dedicated Ubuntu 16.04 VM using Slack as it&amp;rsquo;s user interface.
Create API Key The Hubot interface needs access to the Slack API. This is granted through a bot API token.
 Log into Slack via the web portal and browse to new bot page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>